Guide to the George P. Garrett Papers, 1929-2008 (bulk 1960-2000)
George P. Garrett papers 1929-2008 (bulk 1960-2000)
- Writings Series, 1957-1996 and undated
  - Writings by Garrett Subseries, 1957-1996 and undated
    - Short Stories
      - Rehabilitation, (1 folder)
      - Requiem, (1 folder)
      - The Return, (1 folder)
      - Ride on a Magic Carpet, (1 folder)
      - The Right Thing to do at the Time, (1 folder)
      - Romantic Odelisque, (1 folder)
      - Rose Bush, (1 folder)
      - Ruthe-Anne, (1 folder)
      - Sarah Sue, (1 folder)
      - The Savages, (2 folders)
      - Season's Greetings, (1 folder)
      - Shame, (1 folder)
      - She Hasn't Stopped Talking Yet, (1 folder)
      - She Shall Have Music, (2 folders)
      - She was over eager..., (1 folder)
      - Short Poem for Tall Susan, (1 folder)
      - Signs of Glory, (1 folder)
      - Sin Behind the Eyes, (1 folder)
      - Six Poems by GPG, (1 folder)
      - Some Occasional Stories, (1 folder)
      - Sonneteers, (1 folder)
      - The South, (1 folder)
      - Spring Comes from the South, (1 folder)
      - Standing before them..., (1 folder)
      - Steal Away, (1 folder)
      - Strangers to the Town, (1 folder)
      - Striptease without Music (, (1 folder)
      - Suddenly Everyone Started to Cry (, (2 folder)
      - Susannah of the Suburbs, (1 folder)
      - Thus at the Metropolitan Museum, (1 folder)
      - Then and There, (1 folder)
      - There is No Sense in It, (1 folder)
      - Tide Turning, (1 folder)
      - Time is all destinations and adieus..., (1 folder)
      - To Guess the Riddle..., (3 folders)
      - To Whom Shall I Call...?, (2 folders)
      - Tram Rides, (1 folder)
      - Transition, (1 folder)
      - Trophies of the Sun, (1 folder)
      - Twins, (1 folder)
      - Two, (2 folders)
      - Uneasy Muses, (1 folder)
      - U.S. Space Transport Command, (1 folder)
      - Valleities and Vicissitudes, (1 folder)
      - Very Small Electric Chair..., (1 folder)
      - A Very Small One, (1 folder)
      - The Village, (1 folder)
      - The village stood on a hill..., (1 folder)
      - Walk in the Dark, (1 folder)
      - Walls, (2 folders)
      - Walt, the dream..., (1 folder)
      - Warfare of the Heart ( 1 folder)
      - Watercolor, (1 folder)
      - The Way Real Money Smells ( 1 folder)
      - Where are the Abraham's?, (1 folder)
      - Where is the stallion...? ( 1 folder)
      - The Whole Story ( 1 folder)
      - Wind Song, (1 folder)
      - Witness, (1 folder)
      - A World for Mr. Zeer..., (1 folder)
      - Young we are..., (1 folder)
      - Your body is a rare artistic dungeon..., (1 folder)
      - Youth, (1 folder)
    - Reviews
      - Reviews by Garrett of other authors (A-I), (110 folders) (Box WG 38)
      - Reviews by Garrett of other authors (J-Z), (137 folders) (Box WG 39)
      - Year in Review, (11 folders) (Box WG 40)
      - Misc. reviews, (31 folders)
    - Literary Essays and Biographies
      - Literary essays and biographies: A-F, (56 folders) (Box WG 41)
      - Literary essays and biographies: G-S, (53 folders) (Box WG 42)
      - Literary essays and biographies: T-Z (23 folders (Box WG 43)
    - Speeches, (45 folders) (Box WG 44)
    - Serials
      - Serials with contributions by Garrett (A-Se), (55 folders) (Box WG 45)
      - Serials with contributions by Garrett (Sh-Z), (42 folders) (Box WG 46A)
      - Additions to serials: Sewanee Review, Texas Review, and Virginia Quarterly Review (Box WG 46B)
    - Miscellaneous Writings
    - Misc writings under pen name John Towne, (85 folders) (Box WG 47)
    - Unsorted miscellaneous writings by Garrett, (59 folders) (Box WG 48)
    - Unsorted miscellaneous writings by Garrett, (73 folders) (Box WG 49)
    - Unsorted miscellaneous writings by Garrett, (73 folders) (Box WG 50)
    - Unsorted miscellaneous writings by Garrett, (62 folders) (Box WG 51)
    - Unsorted miscellaneous writings by Garrett, (21 folders) (Box WG 52)
    - Unsorted miscellaneous writings by Garrett, (62 folders) (Box WG 53)
    - Unsorted miscellaneous writings by Garrett, (78 folders) (Box WG 54)
    - Unsorted miscellaneous writings by Garrett, (98 folders) (Box WG 55)
    - Unsorted miscellaneous writings by Garrett, (80 folders) (Box WG 56)
    - Unsorted miscellaneous writings by Garrett, (70 folders) (Box WG 57)
    - Unsorted miscellaneous writings by Garrett, (70 folders) (Box WG 58)
    - Unsorted miscellaneous writings by Garrett, (64 folders) (Box WG 59)
  - Writings Edited by Garrett Subseries, 1966-1994 and undated
    Manuscripts, typescripts, and drafts of material from works edited by Garrett. Includes some serials and reference works edited by Garrett. Unarranged.
    - Girl in the Black Raincoat, 1966, (37 folders) (Box WEG 1)
    - Hollins Critic, 1966-1991, (1 folder)
    - Worksheet, 1972, (1 folder)
    - Poultry: A Magazine of Voice, undated, (3 folders)
    - The Sounder Few, 1971, (3 folders)
    - Wedding Cake in the Middle of the Road, 1992, (2 folders)
    - That's What I Like (About the South), 1993, (3 folders)
    - Intro 6: Life As We Know It, 1974, (3 folders) (Box WEG 2)
    - Intro 7: All of Us and None of You, 1974, (2 folders)
    - Intro 8: The Liar's Craft, 1975, (4 folders)
    - Intro 9: Close to Home, 1978, (5 folders)
    - Ploughshares, 1988, (1 folder)
    - Fruits of Autumn, Flowers of Spring, by Bud Foote, undated, (1 folder)
    - Film Anthology, undated, (17 folders) (Box WEG 3)
    - Man and the Movies, 1967, (18 folders)
    - The Writer's Voice, 1973, (3 folders)
    - Film Scripts: miscellaneous notes, undated, (4 folders) (Box WEG 4)
    - from Film Scripts 1, 1971, (6 folders)
    - from Film Scripts 2, 1971, (2 folders)
    - from Film Scripts 3, 1971, (5 folders)
    - from Film Scripts 3, 1972, (2 folders) (Box WEG 5)
    - from Film Scripts 4, 1972, (8 folders)
    - from Film Scripts 5, 1974, (1 folder)
    - from Film Scripts 6, 1974, (4 folders)
    - Dictionary of Literary Biography, 1993 & 1994, (2 folders)
    - Writers in Va. Directory, 1989, (1 folder)
    - Lecture guides, 1988, (1 folder)
    - Festival '88, 1988, (1 folder)
    - Interviews at Hollins Conference, 1971, (21 folders) (Box WEG 6)
    - Material for film anthology, undated, (14 folders) (Box WEG 7)
    - Botteghe Oscure Reader, 1973, (1 folder)
    - Miscellaneous writings edited by Garrett, 1973-1988 and undated, (21 folders)
  - Proofs Subseries, ca. 1961-1993 and undated
    Proofs of works by Garrett and other authors, including one for Reynolds Price, with notes, revisions, or marginalia. Unarranged.
    - Garrett, George, Poison Pen, 1986, (2 copies) (Box P 1)
    - Garrett, George, Death of the Fox, 1971, (2 folders)
    - Garrett, George, Death of the Fox: misc. front material, 1971, (1 folder)
    - Garrett, George, The Succession, 1983, (1 folder)
    - Garrett, George, Entered from the Sun, 1990, (1 folder)
    - Garrett, George, The Year in the Novel, 1990?, (1 folder)
    - Garrett, George, Book Reviewing in America, undated, (1 folder)
    - Garrett, George, That's What I Like (About the South), 1993, (3 folders)
    - Garrett, George, The Wedding Cake in the Middle of the Road, 1992, (1 folder)
    - Abbott, Lee K., Living After Midnight, 1991
    - Davis, Paxton, Being a Boy, 1988
    - Epstein, Joseph, The Goldin Boys, 1991
    - Hagy, Alyson, Hardware River, 1991
    - Hersey, John, Key West Tales, 1993
    - Leamon, Warren, Unheard Melodies, 1983
    - McMurtry, Larry, Streets of Laredo, 1993
    - Price, Reynolds, Collected Stories, 1993
    - Talese, Gay, Unto the Sons, 1992
    - Wiggins, Marianne, Bet They'll Miss Us When We're Gone, 1991
    - Garrett, George, Do, Lord, Remember Me, 1965, (3 folders) (Box P 2 (oversize))
    - Garrett, George, Death of the Fox, 1971, (2 folders)
    - Garrett, George, The Magic Striptease, 1973, (2 folders)
    - Garrett, George, The Succession, 1983, (4 folders)
    - Garrett, George, To Whom Shall I Call Now in my Hour of Need?, 1965, (1 folder)
    - Garrett, George, Which Ones Are the Enemy?, 1961, (1 folder)
    - George Garrett, James Jones, 1984 (Box P 3 (oversize))
    - George Garrett, Intro 6, Part II, 1974
    - George Garrett, Intro 7, All of Us and None of You, 1974
    - George Garrett, Intro 9, Close to Home, 1978
    - George Garrett, Sorrows of Fat City, 1992
    - Stratford-Upon-Avon Studies 7, 1965, ed. by John Russell Brown and Bernard Harris
    - Dillard, R. H. W., After Borges, 1972
  - Writings by Others Subseries, ca. 1970-1994 and undated
    Manuscripts, typescripts, and photocopies of literary work sent to Garrett by students and other authors. Some items include letters by the author or comments and suggestions by Garrett. Arranged alphabetically by the author's name. Unless otherwise specified, each author's work is contained in one folder.
    - Ackerman, Diane, Brainstorm Sonata: A Profile of the Comprehensive Muse (Box WO 1)
    - Abrams, Gordon, Diamond
    - Adams, Ralph, On the Photographs of my Lai
    - Adams, Richard P., Report on the Manuscript, Faulkner: A Critical Interpretation
    - Aeschliman, M.D., Frederick Buechner & the Virtue of Faith, (2 folders)
    - Albrecht, F., Helen
    - Aldridge, John, Talents & Technicians
    - Allen, James B., Poems
    - Alley, Henry, Umbrella of Glass
    - Alter, Stephen, Rehuka, (2 folders)
    - Anders, Shirley B., The Bus Home
    - Anderson, Scott, The Poetry of Nothing
    - Andrews, Tom, The Brothers' Country
    - Anita, Compartments on a Train
    - Antrim, Donald, Up Above the Houses
    - Appleman, Philip, Shame the Devil
    - Armstrong, Robert G., There's Got to be a Dream First
    - Arrowsmith, William, The Future of Teaching
    - Aufranc, St. George Tucker, Linda, Diaspora, Molly Trencher
    - Ayers, Edward L., What We Talk About When We Talk About the South
    - Bagg, Robert, Euripides' Hippolytos
    - Bagg, Robert, Body Blows
    - Baird, John, Miscellaneous notes
    - Baker, Julie, The Ship
    - Baker, Sheridan, Hawthorne's Evidence
    - Baldwin, William, The Hard to Catch Mercy, (3 folders)
    - Barks, Coleman, Poems
    - Barns, Jim, La Plata Cantata
    - Barney, Stephen A., Poems
    - Barnstone, Willis, Lope's Leonido: An Existential Hero
    - Barnstone, Willis, Leap from the Gargoyle
    - Barnstone, Willis, Poems
    - Barr, Tina, Moving to the Country
    - Barrio, Raymond, The Masqueraders' Ball, Bob Flyrma Vs. the Oberlin Clan & The Burning Path
    - Barrio, Raymond, The Unknown Writer
    - Barrio, Raymond, Making My Love Fair ...Making My Love Dandy
    - Basler, Roy P., The Taste of It: Observations on Current Erotic Poetry (Box WO 2)
    - Batteston, Marton, Poems for Advent & Christmas
    - Battleston, Marton, Osborne's Tom Jones: Adapting a Classic, (2 folders)
    - Battestin, Martin, Fielding & Master Punch in Panton Street
    - Battestin, Martin, Fielding's Revisions of Joseph Andrews
    - Battestin, Martin, Pictures of Fielding
    - Baumbach, Johnathan, From A to Antonioni: Hallucinations of a Movie Addict
    - Bausch, Richard, The Sorrows of Fat City
    - Bausch, Robert, Dog Star
    - Bausch, Robert, The Six Unfinished Stories of Millicent Starks
    - Bell, Charles G., Prodigal Father--From the Third Kingdom
    - Bell, Charles G., Prospectus
    - Bell, Madison, The Structure & Meaning of the Telephone Company
    - Bell, Madison, Paper for Conference on Southern Literature, (2 folders)
    - Bell, Madison, The Structure & Meaning of Dormitory & Food Services
    - Bell, Madison, Interviews w/ the Unfamous & Other Stories
    - Bell, Madison, Interview of Garrett
    - Bell, Madison, George Garrett
    - Belton, Don, Untitled novel
    - Berg, Scott, Goldwyn; A Biography
    - Berry, D.C., Untitled
    - Berry, Jason, Who was William Shakespeare?, Assault on Innocence
    - Biddle, Wayne, The Letters
    - Biguenet, John, Bicycle
    - Blanchard, Heather Lee, Nuntron & the Wart-Nosed People
    - Boorstim, Daniel, Cleopatra's Nose
    - Borkland, Herb, A Lesson From the Master
    - Borgotta, Edgar, Sidesteps Toward a NonSpecial Theory
    - Bornhouser, Fred, A Tree of Five Poems
    - Bowen, M. C., The Departure
    - Bowers, Neal, Outsidein; Brendan Galvin's Poetry
    - Bradham, Jo Allen, Notes
    - Brock, Van, Novas & Other Poems, (2 folders) (Box WO 3)
    - Broughton, Connie & Irv, B.M.O.C.
    - Broughton, Irv, A Little Future in Countries
    - Brown, Ashley, The Short Story In The South: A Review Essay
    - Brown, Jerry, Southern Humor and Roy Blount's Genius
    - Brown, Jerry, You Must Be Present to Win
    - Brown, Larry, Facing the Music
    - Brown, Laura Ellen, Under the Mandlin Moon
    - Brown, Timothy, A Child's Day
    - Bruffee, Kenneth, Edge of the Old One
    - Bryant, J. A. Jr., Criticism in the Post Modern Age
    - Budy, Andrea, Poems
    - Buechner, Frederick, Proof of the Son of Laughter
    - Bukoski, Anthony, Children of Strangers, (2 folders)
    - Bumas, Poison Pen Illustrations
    - Bumpus, Jerry, Lovers
    - Burke, Kenneth, The Party Line
    - Butler, Jack, Voices
    - Calhoun, Susan, Turkish Delights
    - Campbell, Don, Los Angelas Times Book Review; Entered From the Sun
    - Camoin, Francois, Recent Fiction
    - Caples, M. Lopez, Outline
    - Carr, Barnes, Final Edition
    - Carr, Barnes, Shade
    - Carr, Barnes, Right to Privacy
    - Carr, John, Poems
    - Carr, John, Untitled work
    - Carr, John, Poems
    - Carr, John, Strawberry on the Late Asian War
    - Carr, John, Jubilee and other works
    - Carr, John, The Oleander Tapes: A Visit W/ the Dixie Mafia
    - Carrington, Tucker, Revisionist History
    - Carus, Michael, Rose Petals and other poems
    - Cary, Joyce, The Marching Soldier & The Drunken Sailor
    - Casey, John, Spartina, (3 folders)
    - Cassill, AWP 1982
    - Cassill, R. V., Undoing Mind Set
    - Cassill, R. V., In the Central Blue
    - Chamandy, Susan, Signs of Life
    - Chaplin, William, Michelangelo and other poems
    - Chapman, Thomas, Eating Oysters at Johann's and other poems
    - Chapman, Thomas, Portraits and other poems
    - Chappell, Fred, Ancestors
    - Chappell, Fred, Unpeaceable Kingdom
    - Chappell, Fred, The Stranger in the Mirror
    - Chappell, Fred, Forever Mountain
    - Charles, Edna, Excessive Goodness in Timon of Athens and The Good Woman of Setzuan
    - Chenoweth, Avery, Metamorphosis II: the Sequel
    - Cherry, Kelly, Love
    - Cherry, Kelly, Movie Poem
    - Cheuse, Alan, Bones of Light, (3 folders)
    - Cheuse, Alan, Writing it Down for James (Box WO 4)
    - Cheuse, Alan, The Situation of Reviewing
    - Christensen, Paul, Kuzma's Talk Poetry
    - Clark, Geoffrey, Crazy 8's
    - Clark, Geoffrey, Ruffian on the Stair
    - Clem, Robert, As I Lay Dying
    - Cockrell, Nancy, Poems
    - Coe, J. M., The House and the Father
    - Cole, George, Foreword
    - Collins, Billy, The Apple That Astonished Paris
    - Connell, Mary, Mary Connell's Nature Book
    - Constantine, K. C., Various works
    - Cooley, Nizole, Poems
    - Core, George, Life's Bright Parenthesis: Example of Robert Penn Warren
    - Core, George, In the Heart's Ambiguity: Robert Penn Warren as Poet
    - Core, Susan & George, London Theater-Going
    - Cox, Elizabeth, Familiar Ground
    - Criag, Kit, Gone
    - Creagh, Patrick, Poems
    - Crelling, Deanie, An Introduction to a Young Poet-George Garrett
    - Crenshaw, Bill, Leviathan
    - Crews, Harry, The Enthusiast
    - Crow, Doug, Poems and journal entries
    - Cuomo, George, Trial by Water
    - Currier, John, Today
    - Danielson, Patricia, A House w/ No Toys
    - Darr, Ann, Poems
    - David, Cathy, Poems
    - Davis, Lucy, Gate of Dreams (Box WO 17)
    - Davis, Paxton, The Novels of Eric Ambler (Box WO 4)
    - Dawson, Carl, November 1984
    - Dawson, F., Action in Tangent City
    - Dawson, Ruth, Poems
    - Delbanco, Nicholas, The Talking Horse
    - DeLuca, Anna, Poems
    - Devet, Rebecca, Mother Tongue
    - Dew, Joan, Poems
    - Dewey, Mark, Stories
    - Dickey, R.P., Poems (Box WO 5)
    - Dickey, R. P., The Jimmie Cotton Transcripts
    - Dickey, R. P., Self-Liberation
    - Dickey, James, Garrett Intro.
    - Diehl, William, Kill Jack Riley
    - Dillard, R. H. W., The First Man on the Sun
    - Dillard, R. H. W., An Opt For the Carpenter
    - Dillard, R. H. W., Ancient Pistol's Stolen Home
    - Dillard, R. H. W., January
    - Dillard, R. H. W., Guard of Honor: Providential Luck in a Hard-Luck World
    - Dillard, R. H. W., Poems
    - Dillard, R. H. W., "A Lullaby For Mary Grey", "Skelton", "Leeds"
    - Dillard, R. H. W., Translation of You Told Me
    - Dillard, R. H. W., Autobiographical essay
    - Dillard, R. H. W., Poems
    - Dillard, R. H. W., Criticism of Paxton Davis
    - Dillard, R. H. W., Mysteries
    - Dillard, R. H. W., Do Lord Remember Me
    - Dillard, R. H. W., Dance, Wolf, Dance
    - Dillard, R. H. W., "The Death Eaters" and "The Bog: The Naturalist's Notebook"
    - Dillard, R. H. W., Biographical Sketch of Paxton Davis
    - Dillard, R. H. W., Proof of article on Garrett
    - Dillard, R. H. W., "Words for My Students"
    - Dillard, R. H. W., Poems
    - Dillard, R. H. W., Review of A Floating Opera
    - Dillard, R. H. W., Review of The Succession and poems
    - Dillard, R. H. W., Ancient Rituals
    - Dillard, R. H. W., Solar Sailing
    - Dillard, R. H. W., Poems
    - Dellenbeck, Deborah, Afterthought: From A Massage to a Metal Plated Man
    - DiPiero, W. S., Pensieri
    - DiPiero, W. S., Early Light
    - DiPiero, W. S., Some Definitions
    - DiPiero, W. S., Strange in the Dawn (Box WO 6)
    - DiPiero, W. S., The Only Dangerous Thing
    - Doty, Mark, Poems
    - Downer, Alan, The Monitor Image
    - Downer, Alan, Bushranger & Back Woodsman: Notes on The NY Theater 1962-63
    - Drew-Bear, Annette, Miscellaneous articles
    - Dronllard, Lola, Miscellaneous work
    - Eagan, Untitled play
    - Egan, Andrew, The Ice Palace
    - Egbert, Kathy Whitsitt, The 23th Dream
    - Ellis, Gene, Poems
    - Elman, Richard, Poems
    - Elman, Richard, My Sweet Cheat Life In TV
    - Elliott, Lee, Betty Boles
    - Elzinga, Jeff, The Reunion
    - Emerson, Cornelia, Poems
    - Emerson, Nene, Vampire
    - England, David, Mannequins
    - Epps, Garrett, The Floating Island
    - Epps, Garrett, Short story
    - Evanson, Philip, Winton Churchill & the Sinews of Peace
    - Evans, Bob, 7-Minute Draft
    - Ewell, Catch A Falling Star
    - Favazza, Armando, Fellini: Analyst w/o Portfolio
    - Fetsko, Kathye, Harold
    - Finks, Richard, Short stories
    - Fische, Irene, Freeze Frame
    - Fitzpatrick, Nina, Fables of the Irish Intelligensia
    - Flynt, Candace, Sins of Omission
    - Foreman, Steve, Poems
    - Foret, Marguerite, The Forest of Flesh
    - Fowler, Albert, Fools Island
    - Foxworth, Bob, Hawk in the April Wind
    - Franklyn, A. Frderic, Keeno to Cannes: A Journey
    - Friedman, Robert S., Finale
    - Friedman, Robert S., In the Beginning
    - Fuermann, James, The New Year in Houston 1864
    - Galbraith, Joyce, Poems
    - Galvin, Brendan, Dog Love
    - Galvin, Brendan, Hotel Malabar
    - Galvin, Brendan, Poems
    - Galvin, Brendan, The Contemporary Poet & the Natural World
    - Galvin, Brendan, Three Poets
    - Galvin, Brendan, Atlantic Flyaway
    - Galvin, Brendan, Poems
    - Galvin, Brendan, Winter Oysters
    - Galvin, Brendan, Sengekontacket Traveler
    - Galvin, Brendan, Never
    - Gamble, Roberta, Calhoun
    - Garnett, William M., Opus 23 in E Flat
    - Gates, Linda, The Thistle & the Rose
    - Gelfant, Blanche, Faulkner and Keats: The Ideality of Art In The Bear
    - Gelfman, Samuel, The Man From Beyond
    - Gelfman, Kay, Jake was Juggling Oranges
    - Geller, Bruce, Live Now, Pay Later: A Treatment (Box WO 7)
    - Gerhart, Mary & Anthony Yu, Morphologies of Faith: Essays on Religion & Culture in Honor of Nathan Scott Jr.
    - Geyer, Sandra Sue, To Whom It May Concern
    - Giardina, Denise, Storming Heaven
    - Gilbert, Jennifer, Book Review: Whistling in the Dark
    - Gibbons, Richard, Body & Soul
    - Gibson, Margaret, The Writing Teachers
    - Gibson, Dana, A Banker's Daughter
    - Gilbert, Craig, William Faulkner Project Script Draft
    - Gildner, Gary, A Week in South Dakota
    - Gingher, Robert, The Rough Road Home: Stories By NC Writers
    - Gingher, Robert, The Circle
    - Gioia, Dana, The Subculture of Poetry
    - Gioia, Dana, For the Birth of Christ
    - Gioia, Dana, Notes on the New Formalism
    - Goff, Paula, By Path's Coincedent
    - Goldsmith, Maurice Rev., Christmas Sermon
    - Goldstein, Laurence, A Letter to Andrew and Jonathan and other poems
    - Goll, Yvan, The Chaplinade
    - Gottlieb, Elaine, Short stories
    - Gottlieb, Elaine, The Woman Who Was Absent
    - Goyen, William, Recovering: Writing & Healing
    - Graham, John, The Writer's Voice
    - Greer, Ben, Patrick
    - Greiner, Donald, Emerson, Thoreau & Hemingway: Some Suggestions about Literary Heritage
    - Greiner, Donald, American Poets Since WWII
    - Green, Vincent S., Price of Victory: A Novel
    - Gwynn, R. S., The Drive-In
    - Gwynn, R. S., The Narcissiad
    - Gwynn, R. S., The Age of Narcissus
    - Haasse, Hella, The Scarlet City
    - Hagy, Alyson, Madonna on her Back: Stories
    - Hagy, Alyson, Where Men Go To Cry
    - Hall, James B., Old Man Finds What Was Lost
    - Hammond, J., Bilo Blues
    - Hammond, Jerold, Say Hi! to God!
    - Hammond, Jerry, Review of Field of Dreams
    - Hammond, Jerry, Miscellaneous poems and short stories
    - Hammond, Jerry, Fights Tonight-Prufrock At Wasteland Arena
    - Hammond, Essay
    - Hammond, J. S., Untitled story
    - Hampton, Mary, Transformations in Heroic Discourse in Shakespeare and Marlow
    - Handel, Elizabeth, Poems
    - Hankla, Cathryn, The Strawberry Patch
    - Hankla, Cathryn, First Person Love
    - Hankla, Cathryn, Skeleton
    - Hardison, O. B., 3 Types of Renaissance Catharsis (Box WO 8)
    - Hardison, Afternoon Meditation of G. B. R.
    - Harris, Barbara, The Lady With a Taste For Fiction
    - Harris, Marina, A Night Friend
    - Harris, Marina, A Gift
    - Harvard, John, Death of a Shop Teacher
    - Harvard, John M., The Return of Alice to Wonderland
    - Harvard, John M., Third Grade Justice
    - Harvard, John M., Death of the Princeton Owl
    - Harwich, Lynne, Swap Night
    - Harzo, T. A., The Two Faces of Matt Donelson
    - Haysom, Elizabeth, Poems
    - Healy, Eloise, Poems
    - Health, William, Poems and short stories
    - Hemley, Robin, Turning Life Into Fiction
    - Henry, DeWitt, Witness
    - Henry, DeWitt, The Marriage of Anna Maye Potts
    - Henry, DeWitt, The Novels of Brian Moore
    - Henry, DeWitt, At Home
    - Herzig, Jack, Amnesia and Solitaire
    - Herzig, Jack, Short stories
    - Hickland, Austin, We Unburthened Crawl
    - Hicklin, Robert, Synopsis of We Unburthened Crawl and The Brutality of Stone
    - Hillard, Richard, The Winnowing Star
    - Hillard, Richard, My Brother, Death
    - Hillman, Jacques, Review of That's What I Like About the South
    - Hlavsa, James, Faulkner and the Thoroughly Modern Novel
    - Hinrickes, Tom, 15th Summer Writing Workshop
    - Hodges, Harriet, Narcissa
    - Hoffman, Daniel, After the Quarry
    - Hood, Mary, Nobody's Fool, After Moore, and Desire Call of the Wild Hen
    - Horvath, Brooke, Consolation of Ground Zero
    - Horvath, Brooke, Miscellaneous poems
    - Houston, Robert, Invasion of the Bodice Rippers
    - Howes, Barbara, Myself
    - Hoy, Pat C., A Mosaic of Southern Masculinity
    - Hubbard, Bitt, English notebook
    - Huddle, David, Notebook
    - Huddle, David, Contra Nauseam
    - Huddle, David, The Front Yard
    - Huff, Robert, Trio
    - Huebues, Bernard, Poems
    - Huey, Tom, You Could Not Let Me Go
    - Huey, Tommy, Pompeii